Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 2871. Donnelly, Jane: Force Field. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2873. Kirby, Rowan: Shadow Fall. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 723)
  - Harlequin Romance 2874. Neels, Betty: Off with the Old Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2875. Allan, Jeanne: The Waiting Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 724)
  - Harlequin Romance 2876. Armstrong, Lindsay: The Heart of the Matter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2877. Campbell, Bethany: Heartland. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 725)
  - Harlequin Romance 2878. Jameson, Claudia: An Engagement is Announced. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2879. Michaels, Leigh: Sell Me a Dream. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 726)
  - Harlequin Romance 2883. Summers, Essie: High-Country Governess. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2884. West, Nicola: Hidden Depths. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 32, Folder 727)
  - Harlequin Romance 2885. Westwood, Gwen: Bitter Deception. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2886. Wilder, Quinn: To Tame a Wild Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 728)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233570
  - Harlequin Romance 2888. Grant, Vanessa: The Chauvinist. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2889. Goldrick, Emma: Temporary Paragon. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 729)
  - Harlequin Romance 2890. MacGregor, Miriam: Autumn at Aubrey's. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2899. Allan, Jeanne: The Game is Love. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 730)
  - Harlequin Romance 2900. Darcy, Emma: Blind Date. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2901. Roding, Frances: Some Sort of Spell. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 731)
  - Harlequin Romance 2903. Wells, Angela: Desperate Remedy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2905. Arthur, Katherine: Forecast of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 732)
  - Harlequin Romance 2906. Donnelly, Jane: No Place to Run. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2907. Kirby, Rowan: Harmonies. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 733)
  - Harlequin Romance 2908. Martin, Monica: The Buttercup Dream. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2909. Parv, Valerie: Sapphire Nights. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 734)
  - Harlequin Romance 2910. Walker, Kate: Captive Lover. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2911. Campbell, Bethany: Flirtation River. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 735)
  - Harlequin Romance 2912. Clifford, Kay: Recipe for Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2913. Ford, Rachel: Clouded Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 736)
  - Harlequin Romance 2914. Neels, Betty: A Gentle Awakening. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2917. Davis, Deborah: The Healing Effect. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 737)
  - Harlequin Romance 2947. Allyne, Kerry: Beneath Wimmera Skies. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2948. Arthur, Katherine: Send Me No Flowers. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 738)
  - Harlequin Romance 2949. Campbell, Bethany: The Diamond Trap. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2950. Lamb, Charlotte: You Can Love a Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 739)
  - Harlequin Romance 2951. Michaels, Leigh: Strictly Business. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2952. Murray, Annabel: Colour the Sky Red. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 740)
  - Harlequin Romance 2953. Winters, Rebecca: Blind to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2954. Donnelly, Jane: Fetters of Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 741)
  - Harlequin Romance 2955. Mayo, Margaret: Unexpected Inheritance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2956. Neels, Betty: When Two Paths Meet. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 742)
  - Harlequin Romance 2958. Way, Margaret: Devil Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2961. Knoll, Patricia: Always a Bridesmaid. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 743)
  - Harlequin Romance 2962. Shore, Edwina: Storm Clouds Gathering. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2963. Stafford, Lee: Yesterday's Enemy. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 744)
  - Harlequin Romance 2964. Steele, Jessica: Without Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2965. Carter, Rosemary: No Greater Joy. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 745)
  - Harlequin Romance 2967. Goldrick, Emma: The Latimore Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2968. Hammond, Rosemary: Model for Love. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 746)
  - Harlequin Romance 2969. Parv, Valerie: Centrefold. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2970. York, Alison: That Dear Perfection. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 747)
  - Harlequin Romance 2973. James, Dana: Snowfire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2974. Murray, Annabel: Sympathetic Strangers. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 748)
  - Harlequin Romance 2975. Thompson, Marcella: Bed, Breakfast and Bedlam. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2976. Way, Margaret: Mowana Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 749)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233588
  - Harlequin Romance 2977. Charlton, Ann: Ransomed Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2978. Elliot, Rachel: Song of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 750)
  - Harlequin Romance 2978. Elliot, Rachel: Song of Love (second edition). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2979. Hamilton, Diana: The Wild Side. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 751)
  - Harlequin Romance 2980. Hart, Virginia: Without Rainbows (two editions). (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 752)
  - Harlequin Romance 2983. Fox, Susan: Not Part of the Bargain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2984. Goldrick, Emma: Pilgrim's Promise. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 753)
  - Harlequin Romance 2985. Lewty, Marjorie: Bittersweet Honeymoon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2986. Marchant, Jessica: A Stranger's Glance. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 754)
  - Harlequin Romance 2987. Michaels, Leigh: Just a Normal Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2988. Stevens, Lynsey: But Never Love. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 755)
  - Harlequin Romance 2989. Allan, Jeanne: One Reckless Moment. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2990. Allyne, Kerry: Man of the High Plains. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 756)
  - Harlequin Romance 2991. Arthur, Katherine: Through Eyes of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2992. James, Dana: Pool of Dreaming. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 757)
  - Harlequin Romance 2993. Macomber, Debbie: Yours and Mine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2994. Reid, Michelle: Eye of Heaven. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 758)
  - Harlequin Romance 2995. Arden, Jenny: Some Enchanted Evening. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2996. MacGregor, Miriam: Lord of the Lodge. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 759)
  - Harlequin Romance 2997. Michaels, Leigh: Shades of Yesterday. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2998. Scott, Celia: Love on a String. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 760)
  - Harlequin Romance 3001. Jameson, Claudia: Unconditional Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3002. Knoll, Patricia: Send in the Clown. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 761)
  - Harlequin Romance 3003. Mayo, Margaret: Bittersweet Pursuit. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3004. Neels, Betty: Paradise for Two. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 762)
  - Harlequin Romance 3005. Parv, Valerie: Crocodile Creek. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3006. Wells, Angela: Still Temptation. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 763)
  - Harlequin Romance 3007. Clark, Amanda: Blueprint for Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3008. Dawson, Helena: Heart of Marble. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 764)
  - Harlequin Romance 3010. Michaels, Leigh: No Place Like Home. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3011. Steele, Jessica: To Stay Forever. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 765)
  - Harlequin Romance 3012. Way, Margaret: Rise of an Eagle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3013. Armstrong, Lindsay: The Marrying Game. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 766)
  - Harlequin Romance 3014. Arhtur, Katherine: Loving Deceiver. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3015. Day, Samantha: Under a Summer Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 767)
  - Harlequin Romance 3016. Gregory, Kay: A Perfect Beast. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3017. Ker, Madeleine: Troublemaker. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 768)
  - Harlequin Romance 3018. Peters, Sue: Unwillling Woman. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3019. Campbell, Bethany: The Snow Garden. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 34, Folder 769)
  - Harlequin Romance 3020. Jacobs, Lynn: Folly to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3021. Kaye, Judy: Letters of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 770)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233596
  - Harlequin Romance 3022. MacGregor, Miriam: Riddell of Rivermoon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3023. Michaels, Leigh: Let Me Count the Ways. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 771)
  - Harlequin Romance 3024. Neels, Betty: The Fateful Bargain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3025. Gordon, Victoria: Arafura Pirate. (Harlequin Books), 1989;1990 (Box 35, Folder 772)
  - Harlequin Romance 3026. Hammond, Rosemary: Game Plan. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3027. Henaghan, Rosalie: Spell of the Mountains. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 773)
  - Harlequin Romance 3028. Leclaire, Day: Jinxed. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3029. Mayo, Margaret: Conflict. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 774)
  - Harlequin Romance 3030. Rhoades, Sandra K.: Foolish Deceiver. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3033. Donnelly, Jane: When We're Alone. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 775)
  - Harlequin Romance 3034. Duke, Elizabeth: Island Deception. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3035. Forsythe, Melissa: Queen of Hearts. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 776)
  - Harlequin Romance 3036. Neels, Betty: No Need to Say Goodbye. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3037. Allyne, Kerry: Dark Memories. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 777)
  - Harlequin Romance 3038. Macomber, Debbie: A Little Bit Country. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3039. Murrey, Jeneth: Impulsive Proposal. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 778)
  - Harlequin Romance 3040. Scott, Celia: Rumor Has It. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3041. Steele, Jessica: Farewell to Love. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 779)
  - Harlequin Romance 3042. York, Alison: The Maxton Bequest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3043. Arthur, Katherine: Mountain Lovesong. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 780)
  - Harlequin Romance 3044. Carson, Angela: Sweet Illusion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3046. Jameson, Claudia: That Certain Yearning. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 781)
  - Harlequin Romance 3048. Stafford, Lee: A Song in the Wilderness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3049. Beaumont, Anne: Another Time, Another Love. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 782)
  - Harlequin Romance 3052. James, Ellen: Home for Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3053. Neels, Betty: The Chain of Destiny. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 783)
  - Harlequin Romance 3054. Wells, Angela: Rash Contract. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3091. Allison, Heather: Deck the Halls. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 784)
  - Harlequin Romance 3092. Daniels, Val: Silver Bells. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3093. Howard, Stephanie: Master of Glen Crannach. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 785)
  - Harlequin Romance 3094. Ker, Madeleine: Duel of Passion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3098. Gordon, Victoria: Love Thy Neighbor. (Harlequin Books), 1990;1991 (Box 35, Folder 786)
  - Harlequin Romance 3100. Nicholson, Peggy: Burning Dreams. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3101. West, Nicola: A Woman's Place. (Harlequin Books), 1991 (Box 35, Folder 787)
  - Harlequin Romance 3102. Wilson, Patricia: Bond of Destiny. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3104. Clark, Amanda: City Girl, Country Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1991 (Box 35, Folder 788)
  - Harlequin Romance 3106. Thompson, Marcella: Of Rascals and Rainbows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3107. Walker, Kate: The Golden Thief. (Harlequin Books), 1991 (Box 35, Folder 789)
  - Harlequin Romance 3108. Weale, Anne: Thai Silk. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3351. Goldrick, Emma: Leonie's Luck. (Harlequin Books), 1991;1995 (Box 35, Folder 790)
  - Harlequin Romance 3352. Michaels, Leigh: Invitation to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3360. George Catherine: A Brief Encounter. (Harlequin Books), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 791)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233604
  - Harlequin Romance 3361. Leclaire, Day: Mail-Order Bridegroom. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3379. Macomber, Debbie: Brides for Brothers. (Harlequin Books), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 792)
  - Harlequin Romance 3403. Macomber, Debbie: Ending in Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3404. Leclaire, Day: Make believe Engagement. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 793)
  - Harlequin Romance 3405. Wilson, Patricia: A Dangerous Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3406. Hart, Jessica: The Right Kind of Man. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 794)
  - Harlequin Romance 3407. Steele, Jessica: The Marriage Business. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3408. Allan, Jeanne: Moving in with Adam. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 795)
  - Harlequin Romance 3409. Winters, Rebecca: The Badlands Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 3410. Gordon, Lucy: For the Love of Emma. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 796)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Harlequin Publications and Other Publishers
  Series II contains Harlequin publications outside of the Harlequin Romance Series, as well as publications from other publishers.
  - Harlequin Romance 1. Daveson, Mons: Promise Me. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2: Mayo, Margaret: The Marriage Game. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 36, Folder 797)
  - Harlequin Romance 11. Hamilton, Diana: Dark Charade. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 12. Hope, Daphne: Look at My Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 798)
  - Harlequin Romance 14. Kingston, Kate: Bitter Inheritance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 15. Graham, Lynne: Bittersweet Passion. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 799)
  - Harlequin Romance 37. Arden, Jenny: A Taming Hand. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 38. Ford, Rachel: Heirs to Loving. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 800)
  - Harlequin Romance 51. Wilder, Quinn: MacNamara's Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 52. York, Alison: A Secret Truth. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 801)
  - Harlequin Romance 53. Daveson, Mons: No Gentle Encounters. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 54. MacLeod, Jean S.: Legacy of Doubt. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 36, Folder 802)
  - Harlequin Romance 275. Weale, Anne: Seascape. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 276. Gregory, Kay: Man of the Mountains. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 803)
  - Harlequin Romance 279. Richmond, Emma: A Wayward Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 280. Wilder, Quinn: Untamed Melody. (Harlequin Books), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 804)
  - Harlequin Romance 51086. Stuart, Alex: Gay Cavalier. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 51210. Nickson, Hilda: A Friend of the Family. (Harlequin Books), 1967;1968 (Box 36, Folder 805)
  - Harlequin's Collection 1. Winspear, Violet: Lucifer's Angel. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 10. MacLeod, Jean S.: Journey in the Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 806)
  - Harlequin's Collection 11. Burchell, Mary: Wife by Arrangement. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 17. Barrie, Susan: The Stars of San Cecilio. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 807)
  - Harlequin's Collection 19. Burchell, Mary: House of Conflict. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 22. Brett, Rosalind: Sweet Waters. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 808)
  - Harlequin's Collection 23. Blair, Kathryn: Love This Enemy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 25. Baumann, Margaret: When Love is Secret. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 809)
  - Harlequin's Collection 157. Barrie, Susan: The House of the Laird. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 158. Blair, Kathryn: The Primrose Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 810)
  - Harlequin's Collection 159. Conway, Celine: Perchance to Marry. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 163. Malcolm, Margaret: My Tender Fury. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 811)
  - Harlequin's Collection 166. Hunter, Elizabeth: Spiced with Cloves. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 167. Burchell, Mary: Cinderella After Midnight. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 812)
  - Harlequin's Collection 169. Reid, Henrietta: My Dark Rapparee. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Collection 174. Brett, Rosalind: The Bolambo Affair. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 813)
  - Harlequin Presents 778. Ker, Madeleine: Out of This Darkness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Presents 835. Michaels, Leigh: Dreams to Keep. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 36, Folder 814)
  - Harlequin Presents 850. Jordan, Penny: Exorcism. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Presents 871. Armstrong, Lindsay: Finding Out. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 36, Folder 815)
  - Harlequin Presents 879. Bauling, Jayne: Thai Triangle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Presents 937. James, Vanessa: Prisoner. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 37, Folder 816)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233612
  - Harlequin Presents 945. Jameson, Claudia: Adam's Law. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Presents 952. Donald, Robyn: Captives of the Past. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 37, Folder 817)
  - Harlequin American Romance 135. Henry, Anne: A Tough Act to Follow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin American Romance 237. Browning, Pamela: Simple Gifts. (Harlequin Books), 1988 (Box 37, Folder 818)
  - Harlequin American Romance 254. Chambers, Ginger: Call My Name Softly. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin American Romance 298. Sommers, Beverly: A Little Rebellion. (Harlequin Books), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 819)
  - Harlequin Temptation 272. Davis, Maggie: Dreamboat. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Temptation 281. Rafferty, Carin: I Do, Again. (Harlequin Books), 1990 (Box 37, Folder 820)
  - Harlequin Temptation 291. Trent, Lynda: Another Rainbow. (Harlequin Books); "The Best of..." Neels, Betty: The Quiet Professor. (Harlequin Books), 1990;1992 (Box 37, Folder 821)
  - Harlequin Regency Romance. Cresswell, Jasmine: Traitor's Heir. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Salutes 5. Summers, Essie: Adair of Starlight Peaks. (Harlequin Books), 1985;1980 (Box 37, Folder 822)
  - Harlequin Petite 2. Barrie, Susan: Air Ticket. (Harlequin Books); From Harlequin: A Collection of Romantic Notions. (Harlequin Enterprises), 1981;1985 (Box 37, Folder 823)
  - Harlequin's Romantic Short Stories. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin's Romantic Short Stories (second anthology). (Harlequin Books), 1980;1981 (Box 37, Folder 824)
  - Season's Greetings (unnumbered). Tahourdin, Jill: Hummingbird Island. (Harlequin Books); Season's Greetings 469. Seale, Sara: Maggy. (Harlequin Books), 1982;1977 (Box 37, Folder 825)
  - Season's Greetings 562. Hancock, Lucy Agnes: Christmas Gift. (Harlequin Books); Season's Greetings 593. Winspear, Violet: Lucifer's Angels. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 826)
  - Season's Greetings 613. Malcolm, Margaret: The Enemy in His House. (Harlequin Books); Season's Greetings 632. Ives, Averil: Love in the Sunlight. (Harlequin Books); Season's Greetings 798. Weale, Anne: If This is Love. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 827)
  - Christmas Treasures. Macomber, Debbie: Christmas Masquerade; Seger, Maura: A Gift Beyond Peace. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Omnibus 40. Summers, Essie: Heir to Windrush Hill; Rosalind Comes Home; Revolt - and Virginia. (Harlequin Books), 1990;1976 (Box 37, Folder 828)
  - Silhouette Romance 161. Trent, Brenda: Run from Heartache. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Romance 260. Martin, Ione: The Goldenrain Tree. (Silhouette Books), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 829)
  - Silhouette Desire 1. James, Stephanie: Corporate Affair. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Desire 4. Carey, Suzanne: Kiss and Tell. (Silhouette Books), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 830)
  - Silhouette Desire 16. Major, Ann: Dream Come True. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Desire 99. Major, Ann: Love Me Again. (Silhouette Books), 1982;1983 (Box 37, Folder 831)
  - Silhouette Desire 101. Morgan, Raye: Summer Wind. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Desire 131. Larson, Shirley: To Touch the Fire. (Silhouette Books), 1983;1984 (Box 37, Folder 832)
  - Silhouette Desire 367. Broadrick, Annette: Adam's Story. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Desire 493. Gordon, Lucy: Vengeance is Mine. (Silhouette Books), 1987;1989 (Box 37, Folder 833)
  - Silhouette Special Edition 31. Baxter, Mary Lynn: Tears of Yesterday. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Special Edition 74. Wisdom, Linda: Unspoken Past. (Silhouette Books), 1982;1983 (Box 37, Folder 834)
  - Silhouette Special Edition 95. Doyle, Emily: A Matter of Trust. (Silhouette Books); Silhouette Special Edition (unnumbered). Palmer, Diana: The Australian. (Silhouette Books), 1983;1985 (Box 37, Folder 835)